A Guide to the Press Office Records of Virginia Governor George F. Allen, 1993-1998
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Photographs, 1993-1998., Extent: 5.4 cubic feet. (Box 26-37)
  - 1995.
    - Varina All-Star Baseball Team, Junior League Champs, 1995 September 26. (Box 27, Folder 110)
    - Southeast Tourism Awards (Mrs. Allen in Florida), 1995 September 10. (Box 27, Folder 111)
    - Gateway 2000 Anniverary/Press Conference, 1995 September 29. (Box 27, Folder 112)
    - Breast Cancer Awareness, 1995 October 2. (Box 27, Folder 113-114)
    - State Surplus Computers to Schools Press Conference, 1995 September 14. (Box 27, Folder 115-117)
    - Press Conference: Sweet Hunger, 1995 October 16. (Box 27, Folder 118)
    - State Library Site, 1995 October 18. (Box 27, Folder 119)
    - Picnic for Cancer Patients, 1995 October 28. (Box 27, Folder 120-121)
    - Solarex Groundbreaking, 1995 October 16. (Box 27, Folder 122)
    - Red Onion Prison Groundbreaking, 1995 October 3. (Box 27, Folder 123)
    - Annual Indian Tax Presentation (Executive Mansion), 1995 November 22. (Box 27, Folder 124)
    - Partnerships in Education Awards Reception, 1995 November 27. (Box 27, Folder 125)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting (First Family and Governor Allen's Mother), 1995 December 6. (Box 27, Folder 126)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting (Governor and Mrs. Allen), 1995 December 6. (Box 27, Folder 127)
    - Commission on Juvenile Justice, 1995 December 20. (Box 27, Folder 128)
    - State Capitol, 1995. (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Virginia Survey Foundation, 1995 December 21. (Box 27, Folder 130-131)
    - Virginia Amateur Athletes, 1995 December 21. (Box 27, Folder 131)
    - Fire Chiefs' Association, 1995 December 21. (Box 27, Folder 132)
    - Firefighters' Association, 1995 December 21. (Box 27, Folder 133)
    - Boating Safety Award, 1995 December 21. (Box 27, Folder 134)
    - Brenco Tour in Hopewell, 1995 April 12. (Box 27, Folder 135)
    - Governor's Commission on Citizen Empowerment, 1995 May 26. (Box 27, Folder 136-138)
    - Bill Signing: Deadbeat Dads, 1995 March 24. (Box 27, Folder 139)
    - Governor Inaugurates HOV-2 on I-66, 1995 March 1. (Box 27, Folder 140)
    - Margaret Thatcher Addressing the General Assembly, 1995 February 3. (Box 27, Folder 141-142)
    - RV Tour: First Day, Pocahontas Park, 1995 July 10. (Box 27, Folder 143-144)
    - Swearing-in: Bob Metcalf, 1995 January 2. (Box 27, Folder 145)
    - UVA-Virginia Tech Football Players Press Conference, 1995 January 5. (Box 27, Folder 146)
    - Fauquier County Tourism Ceremony, 1995 January 18. (Box 27, Folder 147)
    - Virginia Muscular Dystrophy Association, 1995 January 18. (Box 27, Folder 148)
    - Engineer Week Proclamation Presentation, 1995 January 18. (Box 27, Folder 149)
    - State of Israel, 1995 January 18. (Box 27, Folder 150)
  - 1996.
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of Governor Allen in the Executive Mansion, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 151)
    - Children's Choir in Rotunda, 1996 January 23. (Box 27, Folder 152)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of Mrs. Allen, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 153)
    - Juvenile Justice Press Conference, 1996 January 31. (Box 27, Folder 154)
    - National Sports Day (First Lady), 1996 February 1. (Box 27, Folder 155)
    - Leadership Institute of Peninsula, 1996 February 1. (Box 27, Folder 156)
    - Virginia Society for Human Life, 1996 February 1. (Box 27, Folder 157)
    - Miscellaneous Virginia Tech Football Photographs, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 158)
    - Bill Signing: Dulles Greenway, 1996 February 13. (Box 27, Folder 159)
    - Circus, 1996. (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - Welfare to Work Transition, 1996 February 19. (Box 27, Folder 161)
    - Miscellaneous Research Park Photographs, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 162)
    - Top Leaders at Mary Baldwin, 1996 February. (Box 27, Folder 163)
    - United We Stand Meeting, 1996 February 20. (Box 27, Folder 164)
    - Exchange Students, 1996 February 20. (Box 27, Folder 165)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of Governor Allen and Mrs. Allen in Executive Mansion, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 166)
    - Mrs. Allen at Fine Arts Museum for Faberge Exhibit, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 167)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of Governor Allen with Police Officers, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 168)
    - First Lady with Elementary School Students, 1996 February 23. (Box 27, Folder 169)
    - Air Force Proclamation Ceremony, 1996 February 20. (Box 27, Folder 170)
    - HB433, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Governor Allen's Birthday, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 2-5)
    - Pittston Relocates to Richmond, 1996 March 15. (Box 28, Folder 6-8)
    - Miscellaneous Unidentified Photographs, 1996 March 20. (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
    - Nissan Check Presentation, 1996 March 21. (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
    - Education Press Conference, 1996 March 25. (Box 28, Folder 13-15)
    - Advisory Committee to First Lady, 1996 March 29. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Navy League, 1996 March 29. (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Bill Signing: BPOL (Chamber of Commerce in Fairfax), 1996 April 13. (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Bill Signing: HB422, 1996 April 5. (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Bill Signing: Toshiba/IBM, 1996 April 8. (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Bill Signing: Juvenile Justice, 1996 April 9. (Box 28, Folder 21-24)
    - Environmental Conference (VMI), 1996 April 11. (Box 28, Folder 25-26)
    - VMI Cadets, 1996 April 11. (Box 28, Folder 27-28)
    - Governor at VMI, 1996 April 11. (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Tree Planting at Capitol Square, 1996 April 12. (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Mrs. Allen Riding a Bike, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 31-35)
    - Veterans Cemetery (Amelia County), 1996 April 24. (Box 28, Folder 36-38)
    - Corps of Cadets at Virginia Tech, 1996 April 25. (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Executive Mansion Exterior, 1996 April 29. (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Capital One Ribbon Cutting (Innsbrook), 1996 April 30. (Box 28, Folder 41-42)
    - Frito Lay Annoucement (Lynchburg), 1996 May 2. (Box 28, Folder 43-44)
    - Unidentified Photographs (Trade Mission?), 1996. (Box 28, Folder 45-46)
    - Governor Allen in a Meeting, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Unidentified Ribbon Cutting, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Governor's Children Selling Lemonade at Mansion, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 49-51)
    - Arrival from Trip (State Hangar), 1996 May 24. (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Virginia War Memorial Ceremony, 1996 May 27. (Box 28, Folder 53-55)
    - Asian Trade Mission, 1996 May. (Box 28, Folder 56-66)
    - Dalton Clinic Graduation (MCV Hospital), 1996 May 29. (Box 28, Folder 67-69)
    - Unidentified Photographs (Asian Trade Mission?), 1996. (Box 28, Folder 70)
    - Virginia Fatherhood Campaign, 1996 May 31. (Box 28, Folder 71-72)
    - Members of Parliament, 1996 June 3. (Box 28, Folder 73)
    - Bob Dole at Pheasant Run Sub-Division, 1996 June 4. (Box 28, Folder 74-75)
    - Drake Extrusion, Inc., 1996 June 5. (Box 28, Folder 76-78)
    - Blueridge Aquaculture, 1996 June 5. (Box 28, Folder 79)
    - Step Award Ceremony (First Baptist Church), 1996 June 6. (Box 28, Folder 80-84)
    - Olympic Torch at City Hall (Richmond), 1996 June 10. (Box 28, Folder 85-86)
    - Reynolds Announcement in Russell County (Groundbreaking), 1996 June 14. (Box 28, Folder 86-87)
    - RV: Virginia Inland Port in Warren County, 1996 June 17. (Box 28, Folder 88-89)
    - Domino's Pizza Welfare Reform (Governor Allen and Senator Warner), 1996 June 17. (Box 28, Folder 90-91)
    - RV: Riverview Restaurant in Fredericksburg, 1996 June 17. (Box 28, Folder 92)
    - RV: Cowart Seafood in Lottsburg, 1996 June 18. (Box 28, Folder 93-94)
    - RV: Menhaden Fishing Tour Luncheon, 1996 June 18. (Box 28, Folder 95)
    - RV: Ampro Fisheries, 1996 June 18. (Box 28, Folder 96-97)
    - RV: Lancaster Middle School in Kilmarnock, 1996 June 18. (Box 28, Folder 98)
    - RV: Tug Boat Tour, 1996 June 20. (Box 28, Folder 99)
    - RV: Craney Island, 1996 June 20. (Box 28, Folder 100-102)
    - BMW Car for Olympic Torch Relay, 1996 June 20. (Box 28, Folder 103-104)
    - RV: Girls' State in Farmville, 1996 June 21. (Box 28, Folder 105-106)
    - RV: Boys' State in Lynchburg, 1996 June 21. (Box 28, Folder 107-109)
    - Olympic Torch Relay at Tredegar Iron Works, 1996 June 21. (Box 28, Folder 110-111)
    - Willard Scott of NBC at Executive Mansion, 1996 June 24. (Box 28, Folder 112-113)
    - RV: Southside Community College, 1996 June 24. (Box 28, Folder 114)
    - RV: Danville Community College, 1996 June 24. (Box 28, Folder 115-116)
    - RV: CDBG and IDEA Grant Project Presentation (Martinsville and Henry County), 1996 June 24. (Box 28, Folder 117)
    - RV: Vaughan Furniture Company (Patrick County), 1996 June 24. (Box 28, Folder 118-120)
    - RV: Magnolia Manufacturer, 1996 June 25. (Box 28, Folder 121-122)
    - RV: Marion Composites Facility, 1996 June 25. (Box 28, Folder 123-125)
    - RV: Route 58 in Marion, 1996 June 25. (Box 28, Folder 126)
    - RV: Bristol Compressors, 1996 June 25. (Box 28, Folder 127-128)
    - RV: Bonfire Restaurant in Abingdon, 1996 June 25. (Box 28, Folder 129-130)
    - RV: WCYB-TV in Bristol, 1996 June 26. (Box 28, Folder 131)
    - RV: Natural Tunnel State Park (DARE), 1996 June 26. (Box 28, Folder 132-133)
    - RV: IDA Board in Scott County, 1996 June 26. (Box 28, Folder 134)
    - RV: Super Sak, Inc. in Lee County, 1996 June 26. (Box 28, Folder 135-137)
    - RV: Big Stone Gap Trail, Lonesome Pine, 1996 June 26. (Box 28, Folder 138-139)
    - RV: Wallen Ridge Prison, Big Stone Gap, 1996 June 27. (Box 28, Folder 140-142)
    - RV: Appalachia Senior Center, 1996 June 27. (Box 28, Folder 143-145)
    - RV: Clinch Valley College in Wise County, 1996 June 27. (Box 28, Folder 146)
    - RV: Breaks Interstate Park, 1996 June 27. (Box 28, Folder 147)
    - RV: Appalachia School of Law, 1996 June 28. (Box 28, Folder 148-149)
    - RV: Pocahontas State Park, 1996 June 28. (Box 28, Folder 150)
    - RV: Dedication of C. Jefferson Stafford Highway, 1996 June 28. (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
    - RV: A.O. Smith GOF in Botetourt County, 1996 July 1. (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
    - RV: Meadville Forging in Buchanan County (Groundbreaking), 1996 July 1. (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
    - RV: Douthat State Park in Millboro, 1996 July 1. (Box 29, Folder 7-9)
    - RV: Kim Stan Landfill in Alleghany County, 1996 July 1. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - RV: Warm Springs, 1996 July 2. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - RV: Rowe's Family Restaurant in Staunton, 1996 July 2. (Box 29, Folder 12-13)
    - RV: Wildlife Center in Waynesboro, 1996 July 2. (Box 29, Folder 14-15)
    - RV: One Year Anniversary of Welfare Reform, 1996 July 3. (Box 29, Folder 16-17)
    - RV: Old Country Buffett in Charlottesville, 1996 July 3. (Box 29, Folder 18-19)
    - RV: Parade, 1996 July 4. (Box 29, Folder 20-21)
    - Ann Bancroft with Governor Allen in the Rotunda, 1996 July 17. (Box 29, Folder 22-23)
    - RV: Country Store in Madison County, 1996 July 3. (Box 29, Folder 24-28)
    - National Guard Hangar, 1996 July 18. (Box 29, Folder 29-30)
    - Tax Commission First Meeting, 1996 July 18. (Box 29, Folder 31-33)
    - Touchdown at Airport in Melfa, 1996 July 19. (Box 29, Folder 34-35)
    - Onarock Dock Boat Trip to Tangier, 1996 July 19. (Box 29, Folder 36-37)
    - Tangier Island Tour and Lunch, 1996 July 19. (Box 29, Folder 38-42)
    - Island House Restaurant in Wachapreague, 1996 July 19. (Box 29, Folder 43-44)
    - Cherrystone Aqua Farm in Cheriton, 1996 July 19. (Box 29, Folder 45-47)
    - USN 73 George Washington, 1996 July 22. (Box 29, Folder 48-55)
    - Agency Head Meeting at VCU, 1996 July 24. (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - Fall River Renaissance Press Conference, 1996 July 25. (Box 29, Folder 57-58)
    - Gateway 2000 Grand Opening, 1996 July 26. (Box 29, Folder 59-62)
    - Logistics Management, 1996 July 24. (Box 29, Folder 63)
    - Environmental Stewardship Commission Meeting, 1996 July 30. (Box 29, Folder 64-65)
    - Swearing-in of Tillet and Dewey, 1996 July 30. (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - Operation Break Through in Newport News, 1996 July 31. (Box 29, Folder 67-68)
    - Coleman Bridge in York County, 1996 August 2. (Box 29, Folder 69-71)
    - Capps Police Training Center in Virginia Beach, 1996 August 2. (Box 29, Folder 72)
    - Alcatel Data Ribbon Cutting in Loudoun County, 1996 September 9. (Box 29, Folder 73-74)
    - Dulles Expansion Dedication, 1996 September 5. (Box 29, Folder 75-76)
    - Alexandria Chamber of Commerce, 1996 September 5. (Box 29, Folder 77)
    - Unidentified Photographs, 1996 September 7. (Box 29, Folder 78)
    - GOP Convention, 1996 August 12. (Box 29, Folder 79-83)
    - Governor Allen with George Bush, 1996 September 12. (Box 29, Folder 84-86)
    - Kecoughton High School in Hampton, 1996 September 13. (Box 29, Folder 87)
    - Breast Cancer Reception with Senator Warner at Executive Mansion, 1996 September 16. (Box 29, Folder 88)
    - Thomas Edison High School in Alexandria, 1996 September 11. (Box 29, Folder 89)
    - Fox Morning News, 1996 September 11. (Box 29, Folder 90)
    - Jamestown Colony Announcement, 1996 September 12. (Box 29, Folder 91-92)
    - Cave Spring High School in Roanoke, 1996 September 17. (Box 29, Folder 93)
    - Twin Springs High School in Scott County, 1996 September 17. (Box 29, Folder 94-95)
    - JFK High School, 1996 September 18. (Box 29, Folder 96-97)
    - European Trade Mission (Hapsburg Palace, Austria), 1996 September 27. (Box 29, Folder 98)
    - Governor's Environmental Excellence Award, 1996 October 3. (Box 29, Folder 99-100)
    - Iceland Seafood in Newport News, 1996 October 4. (Box 29, Folder 101)
    - Henricus Park in Chesterfield County, 1996 October 9. (Box 29, Folder 102-105)
    - Oracle Announcement in Fairfax County, 1996 October 9. (Box 29, Folder 106-107)
    - Monument Dedication in Valley Forge, Pennsylvania, 1996 October 11. (Box 29, Folder 108-111)
    - Sumitomo Anniversary in Chesapeake, 1996 October 11. (Box 29, Folder 112-115)
    - Mike Utley in Colonial Williamsburg, 1996 October 14. (Box 29, Folder 116-117)
    - Dedication of Pocahontas Building, 1996 October 16. (Box 29, Folder 118)
    - Virginia Transportation Conference at VMI (Lexington), 1996 October 17. (Box 29, Folder 119-120)
    - Red Carpet Tour in Southwest Virginia, 1996 October 17. (Box 29, Folder 121-124)
    - Clinch Valley College Reception, 1996 October 17. (Box 29, Folder 125)
    - Key Exchange and Ribbon Cutting Ceremony in Cumberland Gap, 1996 October 18. (Box 29, Folder 126-127)
    - Department of Planning and Budget Luncheon at Mansion, 1996 October 22. (Box 29, Folder 128)
    - Workshop on Grassroots/Welfare, 1996 October 23. (Box 29, Folder 129)
    - Guests of Mrs. Allen at the Mansion, 1996 October 23. (Box 29, Folder 130)
    - Virginia Historical Society Groundbreaking, 1996 October 24. (Box 30, Folder 1-7)
    - Mrs. Allen at Tree Planting, 1996. (Box 30, Folder 8-9)
    - New Millenium Studios in Petersburg, 1996 October 7. (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Breast Cancer Awareness Tree Planting, 1996 October 1. (Box 30, Folder 11-12)
    - First Family Greeting Presidential Candidate Bob Dole in Newport News, 1996 October 1. (Box 30, Folder 13-14)
    - Governor's Community Service Award (Virginia Power), 1996 October 25. (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Amvest Mock Debate with Carville, 1996 October 28. (Box 30, Folder 16-17)
    - MCV Breast Cancer Awareness, 1996 October 29. (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Capitol Grounds Tree Planting, 1996 October 29. (Box 30, Folder 19-20)
    - International Association of Arson Investigators, 1996 October 30. (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Family Doctor of the Year, 1996 October 30. (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Fire Safety Week, 1996 October 30. (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Virginia School Principals, 1996 October 30. (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Virginia Small Business, 1996 October 30. (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Pinning of Second Star, General Childers, 1996 October 30. (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Tuckahoe Little League Team, 1996 October 30. (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Odyssey of the Mind, 1996 October 30. (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Goochland High School Academic Team, 1996 October 30. (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Home School Group, 1996 October 31. (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - U.S. Postal Service Stamp, 1996 November 1. (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Keep Virginia Beautiful, 1996 October 30. (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - False Cape State Park, 1996 November 7. (Box 30, Folder 33-34)
    - Richmond Children's Museum Reception, 1996 November 7. (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Repot to Top Management at Hyatt in New York, 1996 November 20. (Box 30, Folder 36-37)
    - Address to General Assembly Members, 1996 November 22. (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Press Conference on Education, 1996 November 22. (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - CSX Santa Train in Southwest Virginia, 1996 November 23. (Box 30, Folder 40-43)
    - Trade Mission to Israel and Europe, 1996 November 11. (Box 30, Folder 44-49)
    - Photo Opportunity: Native Americans, 1996 November 27. (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Indian Tax Ceremony at Mansion, 1996 November 27. (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Prepaid College Tuition (Crestview School), 1996 December 2. (Box 30, Folder 52-53)
    - Family Foundation Reception, 1996 December 2. (Box 30, Folder 54-55)
    - Press Conference with Trish West, 1996 December 4. (Box 30, Folder 56)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting (Allen Family), 1996 December 4. (Box 30, Folder 57-59)
    - Koger Center Social Workers, 1996 December 5. (Box 30, Folder 60)
    - Medal of Life Honors, 1996 December 6. (Box 30, Folder 61)
    - NWB Wiper Blades Groundbreaking, 1996 December 9. (Box 30, Folder 62-64)
    - Agency Head Christmas Party, 1996 December 5. (Box 30, Folder 65)
    - Reception for Press Corps, 1996 December 9. (Box 30, Folder 66)
    - Dedication of Georgia Pacific, 1996 December 10. (Box 30, Folder 67-68)
    - YMCA Indian Princess, 1996 December 10. (Box 30, Folder 69)
    - Group Shot of EPU, 1996 December 10. (Box 30, Folder 70)
    - Ship Building, Inc. in Newport News, 1996 December 11. (Box 30, Folder 71-72)
    - Bank Brothers Manufacturing in Woodstock, 1996 December 12. (Box 30, Folder 73-74)
    - Press Conference at Manchester High School, 1996 December 12. (Box 30, Folder 75-76)
    - Carters Grove Plantation Reception, 1996 December 18. (Box 30, Folder 77-78)
    - Remarks to Business Leaders, 1996 December 17. (Box 30, Folder 79)
    - Electoral College in Old Senate Chamber, 1996 December 16. (Box 30, Folder 80-81)
    - Welfare Reform Press Conference, 1996 December 17. (Box 30, Folder 82)
    - CTB Press Conference, 1996 December 19. (Box 30, Folder 83-84)
    - Report to Money Committee, 1996 December 20. (Box 30, Folder 85)
    - Boise Cascade in Bristol, 1996 December 20. (Box 30, Folder 86-87)
  - 1997.
    - State of the Commonwealth Address, 1997 January 8. (Box 30, Folder 88-91)
    - Barber and Ross Millwork Company Announcement, 1997 January 13. (Box 30, Folder 92)
    - Congress on Information Technology Announcement, 1997 January 14. (Box 30, Folder 93)
    - Hershey Foods Announcement (Stuarts Draft), 1997 January 14. (Box 30, Folder 94-95)
    - Minority Farmers, 1997 January 16. (Box 30, Folder 96-98)
    - Community Learning Week at Virginia Union, 1997 January 17. (Box 30, Folder 99)
    - Westhampton Day School, 1997 January 17. (Box 30, Folder 100-102)
    - Fraternal Order of Police (VDOT), 1997 January 22. (Box 30, Folder 103-104)
    - Metro Sports Backers, 1997 January 22. (Box 30, Folder 105-107)
    - Triple Cross Connector, 1997 January 24. (Box 30, Folder 108-110)
    - Old Capitol Building (Williamsburg), 1997 January 25. (Box 30, Folder 111-112)
    - First Lady in Fight Against Breast Cancer (Virginia Museum of Fine Arts), 1997 January 27. (Box 30, Folder 113)
    - Virginia Technology Summit, 1997 January 29. (Box 30, Folder 114-115)
    - Ericsson Manufacturing in Lynchburg, 1997 January 29. (Box 30, Folder 116-117)
    - Black History Month Kick-off, 1997 January 31. (Box 30, Folder 118-119)
    - Jimmy and Donna Dean, 1997 January 31. (Box 30, Folder 120-121)
    - VADPAC Annual Leadership Dinner (Omni Hotel), 1997 January 31. (Box 30, Folder 122-123)
    - Troops to Bosnia (Fort Pickett), 1997 February 9. (Box 30, Folder 124-130)
    - Congressional Delegation, 1997 February 10. (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
    - Virginia Union University, 1997. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - New Millienium Studios, 1997 February 18. (Box 31, Folder 5-7)
    - Dollar Tree (Chesapeake), 1997 February 25. (Box 31, Folder 8-9)
    - Black History Month Reception, 1997 February 27. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Girl Scout Event in Short Pump, 1997 February 28. (Box 31, Folder 11-14)
    - Easter Seals Kick-a-thon (L.C. Bird High School), 1997 March 1. (Box 31, Folder 15-17)
    - ECI Ribbon Cutting, 1997 March 3. (Box 31, Folder 18-19)
    - Family Dollar (Warren County), 1997 March 5. (Box 31, Folder 20-22)
    - Weed and Seed Program, 1997 March 6. (Box 31, Folder 23-26)
    - DMV License Renewal Tour, 1997 March 7. (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - New Orleans Urban Panel Discussion (Southern Governors' Association), 1997 March 11. (Box 31, Folder 28-29)
    - Bill Signing: Trucking, 1997 March 12. (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Bill Signing: Clean Water, 1997 March 12. (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Bill Signing: Tax Cut, 1997 March 13. (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Bill Signing: Teacher Immunity (Virginia Beach), 1997 March 14. (Box 31, Folder 33-35)
    - Bill Signing: Indian Legislation, 1997 March 14. (Box 31, Folder 36-38)
    - HB2154 / HB2155 / SB925, 1997 March 10. (Box 31, Folder 39-41)
    - Shamrock Pageant, 1997 March 17. (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Joint Drug Trials, 1997 March 17. (Box 31, Folder 43-46)
    - Welfare Reform at St. Stephen's Episcopal Church, 1997 March 18. (Box 31, Folder 47-48)
    - Sailor of the Year, 1997 March 18. (Box 31, Folder 49-50)
    - Sister Cities (Conference Room), 1997 March 19. (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - Ethics Reform Legislation, 1997 March 19. (Box 31, Folder 52)
    - Bill Signing: Cumberland School, 1997 March 19. (Box 31, Folder 53-55)
    - Bill Signing: Buckroe Beach Environmental Legislation, 1997 March 20. (Box 31, Folder 56-57)
    - Veto of HB2213 at BDM Corporation Headquarters, 1997 March 21. (Box 31, Folder 58-59)
    - Mike Mitchner and Family, 1997 March 21. (Box 31, Folder 60)
    - Bill Signing: Parental Notification, 1997 March 22. (Box 31, Folder 61-70)
    - Virginia Council on Economic Education (Federal Reserve Bank), 1997 March 26. (Box 31, Folder 71)
    - Bell Atlantic Plus Announcement, 1997 March 27. (Box 31, Folder 72-75)
    - Bill Signing: HB2885, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 76)
    - Bill Signing: HB2037 and HB2211, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 77-78)
    - Bill Signing: HB2294 and SB753, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 79)
    - Bill Signing: HB2091 and SB799, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 80)
    - Bill Signing: HB2733, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 81)
    - Bill Signing: SB939, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 82)
    - Bill Signing: SB981 and HB2329, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 83)
    - Bill Signing: HB2673, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 84)
    - Bill Signing: HB2266, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 85)
    - Bill Signing: HB1597, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 86)
    - Bill Signing: SB1032, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 87)
    - Bill Signing: SB1019, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 88)
    - Bill Signing: HB1583 / HB 1839 / HB 2534 / HB 2536, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 89-92)
    - Marc A. Heathcock, 1997 April 1. (Box 31, Folder 93)
    - Day of Prayer (Landes), 1997 April 2. (Box 31, Folder 94)
    - Bill Signing: HB2682, 1997 April 2. (Box 31, Folder 95)
    - Bill Signing: HB826 (Ruff), 1997 April 2. (Box 31, Folder 96)
    - Bill Signing: HB1115 (Ruff), 1997 April 2. (Box 31, Folder 97)
    - Bill Signing: HB2044 (Wilkins), 1997 April 2. (Box 31, Folder 98)
    - Bill Signing: HB2160 (Rollison), 1997 April 2. (Box 31, Folder 99)